A Guide to the China Medical Board, Inc. records, RG 1 FA065
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), January-April 1947 (Box 47, Folder 331)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), May-October 1947 (Box 47, Folder 332)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), November-December 1947 (Box 47, Folder 333)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1948 (Box 47, Folder 334)
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1949 (Box 48, Folder 335)
    See also Box 162, Folder 11
  - Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC), 1950-1951 (Box 48, Folder 336)
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Report, 1921-1922 (Box 48, Folder 337)
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Report, 1923-1924 (Box 48, Folder 338)
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Report, 1925-1927 (Box 48, Folder 339)
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Report, 1929-1933 (Box 48, Folder 340)
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Report, 1933-1941 (Box 49, Folder 341)
- Director - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Appointment of, 1945-1947 (Box 49, Folder 342)
  Balfour; Ballou; Bowen; Burwell; Director; Fosdick; Greene; Gregg; Hastings; Hu; Keefer; Palmer, Walter; Parker; Sze; Tsur; Van Dyke
- Director, Acting - Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) - Annual Reports, 1929-1935 (Box 49, Folder 343)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 1-12, 1915-1919 (Box 49, Folder 344)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 13-22, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 345)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 23-38, 1919-1921 (Box 49, Folder 346)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 46-71, 1921-1924 (Box 49, Folder 347)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 74-100, 1925-1927 (Box 50, Folder 348)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 103-126, 1927-1929 (Box 50, Folder 349)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 127-139, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 350)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 140-167, 1930 (Box 50, Folder 351)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 168-184a, 1930-1931 (Box 50, Folder 352)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 185-186, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 353)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 197-205, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 354)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 206-210, 1932 (Box 51, Folder 355)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 211-218, 1932-1934 (Box 51, Folder 356)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 220-223, 1934 (Box 51, Folder 357)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 224-231, 1934-1935 (Box 51, Folder 358)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 233-246, 1935 (Box 51, Folder 359)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 248-268, 1935-1936 (Box 51, Folder 360)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 269-275, 1937 (Box 52, Folder 361)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 276-301, 1937-1938 (Box 52, Folder 362)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 303-340, 1939-1947 (Box 52, Folder 363)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 342-368, 1947-1949 (Box 52, Folder 364)
- Documentary Record - Nos. 369-374, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 365)
- Documentary Record - Missing (Box 52, Folder 366)
  Documentary Record - List of Missing Numbers and possible alternative locations; Documents of Record, 1916-1951
  General note
  There are two sets of Documents of Record, one bound and one not. Some documents appear in both sets, some only in one, a few in neither set though these appear in other files throughout the collection. Some have been filed in the Treasurer's Office section, since they were found there when the collection was processed.
- Dr-Du, 1920-1970 (Box 52, Folder 367)
  Draeger Unit, 1939-1940, 1949 (Bowen; Director); Drug Addiction, 1937 (Dietrich); Drug Garden, 1922 (Greene; Houghton); Drugs, 1923, 1937-1938 (Cameron; Houghton); Dudley, E. C., 1921-1923; Dunlap, A. M., 1920, 1945-1947, 1951, 1963, 1970
  Items of special note in this folder include a memo on living expenses (1920), found under the mark-up Dunlap.
- Ed (Box 53, Folder 368)
  Edmiston, Irma R. (Mrs. Bowen), 1924-1926; Edsall, David L., 1926-1928
- Eggleston, Margery K., 1927-1933 (Box 53, Folder 369)
  Items of special note in this folder include "Preliminary Report to Rockefeller Foundation and China Medical Board, Inc." (1933).
- Eggleston, Margery K., 1934-1950 (Box 53, Folder 370)
  Items of special note in this folder include "China Medical Board and Peking Union Medical College (PUMC) Problems" (1934).
- Eggleston, Margery K. - Interviews, 1920-1922 (Box 53, Folder 371)
  Index 1920-1923
- Eggleston, Margery K. - Interviews, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 372)
- Eggleston, Margery K. - Interviews, 1924-1925 (Box 53, Folder 373)
- Eggleston, Margery K. - Interviews, 1926 (Box 54, Folder 374)
- Eggleston, Margery K. - Interviews, 1927 (Box 54, Folder 375)
- Eggleston, Margery K. - Interviews, 1928 (Box 54, Folder 376)
- Eggleston, Margery K. - Interviews, 1929-1935 (Box 54, Folder 377)
- Ell-Elo (Box 54, Folder 378)
  Elliott, K. A. C., 1964-1966; Ellis, A. G., 1923, 1936-1937; Eloesser, Leo, 1947-1949
  Items of special note in this folder include a chart of the Organization of Medical Science and Teaching in Peking, found under the mark-up Elliott, K. A. C.
- Elsmith, Dorothy O. (Mrs. Frederick L. Gates), 1967 (Box 54, Folder 379)
  Buttrick; Flexner, S.; Gates, F. L.; Welch, W. H.
  Items of special note in this folder include historical material: notes on address by W. H. Welch (October 30, 1915); report of itinerary and findings of Special Commission to China by Buttrick (January 17, 1916); report on North China by Welch; report on Hankow and Changsha by Gates; report on Central and Southern China by Flexner; "The Medical Work of Christian Missions in China" by Greene; 2 unidentified photographs.
- Embree, Edwin R., 1917-1925 (Box 54, Folder 380)
- Eme-Ena (Box 54, Folder 381)
  Emergency Fund, 1928 (Gee; Greene; Greene); Emergency Medical Service Training School, 1943-1946 (Chang, P. Y.; Tai, T. Y.); Emslie, William M., 1950-1953, 1956-1958; Enami, Vincent, 1919
  Items of special note in this folder include a letter about negatives made into colored prints, with color designations, found under the mark-up Enami, Vincent.
- Engineer (A-J) (Box 55, Folder 382)
  Alston, William G., 1929, 1933-1934, 1938-1949, 1957, 1971; Chang, Cheng-ping Archie, 1930, 1940, 1945-1950 (See also Engineer - Alston); Jeong, Joe Yuen, 1929
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Alston and C. P. Archie Chang (1946), found under the mark-up Engineer - Alston; and a photograph of Chang and David Miller (1946), found under the mark-up Engineer - Chang, C. P. Archie.
- Ent-Eve (Box 55, Folder 383)
  Entrance Requirements, 1923-1927, 1932-1939 (Carruthers; Director; Greene; Houghton; MacMillan; Wu); Ephedrine (see Pharmacology); Equipment, 1916; Equitable Life Insurance Co., 1947; Evangelical Lutheran Augustana Synod, 1934 (Evald, Emmy); Evans, Joseph, 1921; Evers, A. J., 1927
- Ex (Box 55, Folder 384)
  Exchange, 1920-1922, 1929-1950 (Balfour; Comptroller; Director; Forkner; Forman, D. N.; Grant, S. M.; Greene; Judd, W. H.; Kenzel, M.; Kigg, S. G.; Loucks; Rockefeller, J. D. 3); Experimental Medical School, 1932-1934 (Greene)
  See also Oversized Folder 69, Item 10
- Fai-Fei (Box 55, Folder 385)
  Faircervis, Walter, Jr., 1947; Famine Relief, 1920-1921, 1930 (Greene); Fan Memorial Biological Institute, 1932, 1946 (Hu); Fan, Po-sheng (Mrs. Anthony Garra), 1945-1949; Fang, Chi, 1948-1949; Fang Te-ching Memorial Loan Fund, 1932 (Ling); Far Eastern Association of Tropical Medicine, 1923, 1934 (Director; Greene); Fei, Hisao-tung, 1943-1944; Fei, Ki-min, 1948-1950
- Fellowships, 1928-1933 (Box 55, Folder 386)
- Fellowships, 1934-1936 (Box 55, Folder 387)
- Fellowships, 1937-1939 (Box 55, Folder 388)
- Fellowships, 1940-1949 (Box 56, Folder 389)
  American Bureau for Medical Aid to China (ABMAC); Balfour; Director; Gee; Greene; Gregg; Hodgman; Hoeppli; Houghton; Lobenstine; Paris Office; Paris Office - Greene; Robinson; Snapper; Swedish - Berglund; Swedish - Grant; Tai; Thompson; Van Allen; Wong, Wen-hao
- Fellowships - Allocations, 1945-1947 (Box 56, Folder 390)
- Fellowships - Memoranda, 1928-1941 (Box 56, Folder 391)
- Fellowships - Memoranda, 1942-1949 (Box 56, Folder 392)
- Feng (C-Y) (Box 56, Folder 392A)
  Feng, Chih-ying, 1947; Feng, P. C. Paul, 1947, 1954; Feng, Yu-hsiang, 1922-1923, 1926
- Feng, L. C. - Scientific Apparatus and Equipment Report, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 393)
  Items of special note in this folder include a report - Scientific Apparatus and Equipment, Peking Union Medical College (1946-1947).
- Feng, L. C. - Scientific Apparatus and Equipment Report, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 394)
- Ferguson, M. E., 1927-1939 February (Box 56, Folder 395)
- Ferguson, M. E., 1939 March-1941 (Box 56, Folder 396)
- Ferguson, M. E., 1941-1945 (Box 57, Folder 397)
  See also Box 162, Folder 12
- Ferguson, M. E., 1946-1947 (Box 57, Folder 398)
- Ferguson, M. E., 1948-1949 (Box 57, Folder 399)
- Ferguson, M. E., 1950-1951 (Box 57, Folder 400)
  Ajax Steamship; American Express; American President Lines; Aronson, Shepard G.; Boring, Alice; Boynton, Grace M.; British Passport; Chase National Bank; Chen, James S.; Chiu, Philip; Clift Hotel; Hale, Bertram C.; Herod, W. R.; Hirst, E.; Hu, C.; Lee, C. U.; Mutual Life Insurance; National City Bank; New England Mutual; Pacific Transport Lines, Inc.; Parker, Philo W.; Rockefeller Foundation - Grant, John B.; Rockefeller Foundation - Lynn, H. B.; Tsur, Y. T.; Van Dyke, H. B.
- Ferguson, M. E. - Diary, December 9, 1946-March 31, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 401)
- Fetter, Frank W., 1931 (Box 57, Folder 401A)
- Field Studies - Anthropology, 1922-1933 (Box 57, Folder 402)
  Items of special note in this folder include a reprint of articles in Chinese newspapers by Peking Union Medical College staff (Andrews, Barbour, Black, Chardin, Grabau, Pei, Wong, Young) (1930); and a photograph of Peking Man Skull, atached to a letter from Black to Eggleston (April 12, 1930).
- Field Studies - Anthropology, 1934-1936 (Box 57, Folder 403)
  See also Box 162, Folder 13
- Field Studies - Anthropology, 1937-1941 (Box 58, Folder 404)
- Field Studies - Anthropology, 1944-1971 (Box 58, Folder 405)
  Anderson, J. S.; Andrews; Appleget; Barbour (See also Cenozoic Laboratory, 1962); Black; Bohlin; Bowen; de Chardin (See also Cenezoic Laboratory, 1962); Cohn, Alfred; Comptroller; Cowdry, E. V.; Director; Faircervis; Flexner, Simon; Fosdick, Raymond; Geological Survey; Grabau; Greene; Gregg; Gregory; Hanson, Frank B.; Houghton; Irving, John H. B.; King, Sohtsu G.; Mason, Max; Memoranda; Moore, Ruth; Morant, G. M.; National Geological Survey - Kao, P.; Newsweek Magazine; Pei, W. C.; Pinkley, George; Robinson, G. Canby; Simpson, George G.; Thompson, Norma; Ting, V. K.; University of Chicago; Vincent, G. E.; Von Koenigswald (see V); Weaver, Warren; Weidenreich; Wong, W. H.; Woodward, F.; Young
- Field Studies - Anthropology - Black, Davidson, 1926-1933 (Box 58, Folder 406)
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of a restored skull fragment of Peking Man, attached to a letter from Black to Eggleston (August 2, 1930).
- Field Studies - Anthropology - Weidenreich, F., 1934-1940 (Box 58, Folder 407)
  Items of special note in this folder include a statement of expenditures for Human Paleontological Research in Asia (April 1933), attached to a letter from Greene to Eggleston (November 9, 1934); and a photograph of Peking Man Mandible, attached to a letter from Weidenreich to Houghton (October 28, 1936).
- Field Studies - Anthropology - Weidenreich, F., 1941-1944 (Box 58, Folder 408)
- Field Studies - Anthropology - Weidenreich, F., 1945-1947 (Box 58, Folder 409)
- Field Studies - Anthropology - Weidenreich, F., 1948 (Box 58, Folder 410)
- Field Studies - Anthropology - Weidenreich, F., 1949-1964 (Box 59, Folder 411)
  hadwell, H. Marshall; Courville, Cyril B.; Hafner Publishing Co.; Lancaster Press, Inc.; Meridan Gravure Co.; Seiler's Book Store; G. E. Stechert & Co.; Stechert & Hafner
- Field Studies - Kala-Azar, 1922-1926 (Box 59, Folder 412)
- Field Studies - Kala-Azar, 1927-1934 (Box 59, Folder 413)
  Cash, J.R.; Comptroller; Director; Falkenstein, R.B.; Flexner, Simon; Gates, Frederick L.; Gee, N. Gist; Greene; Griffith, Eugene (see G); Hertig, Arthur T.; Hertig, Marshall; Hogg, James S.; Houghton; Hu, C. H.; Hunt, Reid Leiper, R. T.; Mao, H. C.; Peabody, Francis W.; Riley, William A.; Russell, F. F.; Weimer, Byron; Welch, William H.; Wolbach, S. B.; Young, Charles W.
- Field Studies - Schistosomiasis, 1922-1926, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 413A)
  Director; Houghton; Hunt, Reid; Meleney, Henry E.; Wassell, C. McA.
- Fil-Fry (Box 59, Folder 414)
  Filing System, 1949; Firor, Marion P. (Mrs. Oliver B. Johnston), 1929; Flexner, Abraham, 1918-1932, 1949 (See also Elsmith); Florida State Nurses' Association - Reed, Elizabeth, 1948; Foley, William T., 1940; Follwell, Edward H., 1932-1934; Fong, Ching-hsuan, 1947; Ford, D. E., 1958; Foreign Missions Conference of North America, 1929-1930, 1945; Formulary, 1927, 1932 (see Hospital Publications, and Publications); Fraser, Francis, R., 1916; Frazer, E. W., 1917; Freight, 1922-1932, 1937-1941 (Comptroller; Goodrich; Greene; Hogg; Houghton); Friedlander, Mary A., 1928; Fryer, Stanley A., 1931-1934, 1938
- Fu-Ful (Box 59, Folder 415)
  Fu, Show-cheng, 1945; Fu, Sun-yuan, 1945; Fukien Province - Provincial Medical College, 1943-1945; Fulbright Bill, 1946-1949 (Bennett, C. R.; Benton, William; Board of Foreign Scholarships; Board of Foreign Scholarships - Bowles, Gordon T.; Caldwell, O. J.; Director; Holland, Kenneth; Loucks; Marshall, George C.; Mundt, Bill; Pierson, Harry H.; Robinson, Jay; U. S. Education Fund (Caldwell, O. J.; Director; Hodges; Melby, John); Fuller, Stuart J., 1922-1923
- Furloughs, 1921-1939 (Box 59, Folder 416)
  Buttrick; Comptroller; Director; Embree; Goodrich; Greene; Houghton; Peabody; Pearce; Resident Director; Welch
- Furloughs - Memoranda, 1925-1940 (Box 59, Folder 417)
- Ga-Ge, 1925-1940 (Box 59, Folder 418)
  Garrod, Archibald, 1921; Gates, Dorothy O. (Mrs. Frederick T. Gates), (see Elsmith); Gates, Frederick T., 1914-1921, 1929; General Electric Medical Products Co., 1947; German Doctors - Baehr, 1934; Gest Chinese Research Library, 1934 (Blake, Robert P.; Donham, W. B.; Marshall, John; Stevens; Swann, Nancy Lee).
  Items of special note in this folder include "Gradual and Orderly Development of a Comprehensive and Efficient System of Medicine in China" (1914), found in the mark-up Gates.
- Gia-Gor, 1925-1940 (Box 60, Folder 419)
  Giang, Ai-mei (Mrs. Wang Cheng-fu), 1923, 1962; Gifts (Bourne, George L., 1936-1941; Gillis, I. V., 1933; McKhann, Charles F., 1938; Snite, F. B., 1936-1937); Ginling College, 1932, 1945 (Child Guidance Clinic - Cheng, Leslie Y. C.; Greene); Goldwater, S. S., 1922; Goodrich, Anne, 1922; Goodrich, L. Carrington, 1930-1939, 1947, 1952-1966; Gordon, J. Dorothy, 1923, 1959; Gordon, Sara E., 1925-1931
- Governing Council - Minutes, 1938-1949 (Box 60, Folder 420)
- Governing Council - Business Division - Minutes, 1937-1950 (Box 60, Folder 421)
- Governing Council - Educational Division - Minutes, 1937-1939 (Box 60, Folder 422)
- Governing Council - Educational Division - Minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 60, Folder 423)
- Governing Council - Educational Division - Minutes, 1940-1941 (Box 60, Folder 424)
- Governing Council - Educational Division - Minutes, 1947-1951 (Box 60, Folder 425)
- Governing Council - Medical Sciences Division - Minutes, 1937-1939 (Box 61, Folder 426)
- Governing Council - Medical Sciences Division - Minutes, 1939-1941 (Box 61, Folder 427)
- Governing Council - Medical Sciences Division - Minutes, 1947-1950 (Box 61, Folder 428)
- Grab-Grad (Box 61, Folder 429)
  Grabau, Amadeus W., 1937-1951; Grace Hospital, 1925 (Babcock); Graduate Society, 1931-1935, 1941-1944 (Alumni Bulletin, V.II; Balfour, Marshall; Grant, J. B.; Greene; Gregg; Hsu, Hsing-an; Huang, Nancy; Li, Hsiao-hsien; Liu, Shao-kuang; Liu, Shu-wan; Pai, S. E.; Rockefeller, J. D. 3; Wong, Wen-hao); Graduates (Correspondence lists, 1963-1970)
  Items of special note in this folder include Alumni Bulletin, Vol. II (June 1931), found under the mark-up Graduate Society.
- Graduates - Alumni Reception Guest Book, March 26, 1980 (Box 61, Folder 429A)
- Graduates - List, 1957-1959 (Box 61, Folder 430)
- Graduates - List, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 431)
- Graduates - List, 1964-1969 (Box 61, Folder 432)
- Graduation, 1922-1941 (Box 62, Folder 433)
  Director; Greene; Houghton; MacMillan; Resident Director
- Grae-Gree (Box 62, Folder 434)
  Graefe, E., 1927; Graff, 1924-1925; Grafton, W. T., 1922; Graham, Charles T., 1921; Graham, E. R., 1921; Graham, Henry J., 1922, 1925; Grant, Amerlia, 1928; Grant, L. P., 1922; Grasslands Hospital - Hemstead, Almira H., 1948; Graves, William, 1923; Gray, A. L., 1922; Gray, Carl R., 192;3 Green, Alvin, 1928; Greene, Theodore F., 1923; Greene, D. Crosby, 1922; Greene, Jerome D., 1915, 1932 (see also Rockefeller Institute); Greene, Phillips F., 1920, 1923, 1945
- Greene, Roger S., 1916-1935 (Box 62, Folder 435)
  Items of special note in this folder include an interview with President of China, Li Yaan-lung (July 10, 1916); an address on opening of 2nd year of Pre-Medical School (1918); a China Medical Board memo re: Purpose, Policy and Program (1919); an analysis of Proposal for 8 Years Financing of College and China Medical Board, Inc. (1932); "Present Status and Needs for the Peking Union Medical College" (1933); and "General Considerations for Medical Curriculum Requirements in China" (1935).
- Greene, Roger S., 1945-1947 (Box 62, Folder 436)
- Greene, Roger S. - Diary, 1919 (Box 62, Folder 437)
- Greene, Roger S. - Diary, 1920 (Box 62, Folder 438)
- Greene, Roger S. - Diary, 1925-1926 (Box 62, Folder 439)
  See also Box 162, Folder 14
- Greene, Roger S. - Interviews, 1922-1923 (Box 63, Folder 440)
  (Index 1922-1925)
- Greene, Roger S. - Interviews, 1924 (Box 63, Folder 441)
- Greene, Roger S. - Interviews, 1925 (Box 63, Folder 442)
- Greene, Roger S. - Interviews, 1926-1933 (Box 63, Folder 443)
- Greene, Roger S. (Mrs.), 1947-1970 (Box 63, Folder 444)
- Gree-Gunn (Box 63, Folder 445)
  Greene, Theodore C., 1932; Greensfelder, L. E., 1923; Gregg, Alan, 1933 (see also RF Commission, 1946); Gregory, J. W., 1924; Grettor, Lystra E., 1922; Greulich, W. W., 1946; Grey, Ernest, 1928-1929; Griffith, Eugene, 1927; Grimes; H. C., 1916-1917; Groen, J. J., 1947; Grundquist, Clary M., 1932; Grunner, O. Cameron, 1947; Guides, 1922 (Goodrich; Houghton); Gunn, Selskar M., 1931
- Gynecology, 1920-1938 (Box 63, Folder 446)
  Amoss; Chow, Anna; Comptroller; Director; Greene; Houghton; Maxwell; McLean; Pearce; Resident Director
- Gynecology - Staff (A-D) (Box 63, Folder 447)
  Ao, Chu, 1949; Chai, Chan-tsan, 1949-1950; Chan, Bean-chye, 1937-1939, 1946-1950; Chang, Shih-wei, 1930; Chao, Chih-yi, 1948-1950; Chao, Shu-lien, 1934; Chen, Pi-hun, 1950; Chen, P. W., 1949; Cheng, Yu-ho, 1934-1935, 1946-1948; Chiang, Mei, 1949-1950; Chiao, Shu-chu, 1948-1950; Chin, Henry, 1934-1936, 1941-1946, 1954; Chow, Anna, 1933; Chow, Mei-ching, 1949; Chow, Ming-pei, 1948; Chu, I-tah, 1938-1941; Chu, James S., 1924-1926; Chung, Ping-mei, 1930; Clark, John G., 1923; Cooke, Alma L., 1935; Cormack, James G., 1915-1917; Crooks, Emily M., 1930; Cunningham, Gladys S., 1927; Doo, Yoong-yih, 1932
- Gynecology - Staff - Eastman, Nicholson J., 1924-1935, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 448)
- Gynecology - Staff (Fa-Hs) (Box 64, Folder 449)
  Fang, Lien-yu, 1938-1941; Ford, David E., 1919-1922; Gell, Mary P., 1927; Han, Hank-ling, 1941; Han, Mei-ling, 1950; Ho, Pi-hui, 1933; Hoffman, Doris Phoebe, 1923-1926; Hsiung, Vera, 1927; Hsu, Hsiang-lien (Alice), 1937-1938, 1947, 1952, 1957-1960, 1967-1968
- Gynecology - Staff (Hu-Le) (Box 64, Folder 450)
  Huang, Pao-chen (Beulah), 1929, 1933, 1954-1959; Huang, Teh-fang, 1935; King, Gordon, 1927-1932, 1943-1950, 1964; Ko, Ying-kuei, 1933-1935, 1940-1941, 1945; Koah, Zing-sung, 1948-1949; Ku, Yun-yu, 1935-1938, 1945; Kuo, Chuan-ching, 1935-1937; Lam, Kuk-sin, 1936; Lee, Louise (Li, Juilin), 1930-1931, 1945; Lee, Shih-wei, 1926, 1929-1933, 1947
- Gynecology - Staff (Li-Lin) (Box 64, Folder 451)
  Li, Hui-fang, 1941, 1946-1948; Li, Jui-lin (see this file, Lee, Louise); Li, Katherine, 1935; Lien, Li-chuan, 1950; Lim, Kha-ti (Lin, Chiao-chih), 1932-1950, 1971; Lin, Hazel, 1936-1948, 1954, 1958; Lin, Kien-pong, 1941; Lin, Sung, 1933-1941; Lin, Yuan-ying, 1929, 1936, 1947
- Gynecology - Staff (Ling-Ma) (Box 64, Folder 452)
  Ling, Inez (Lin Ai-yueh), 1937; Ling, Yung-tung, 1941; Liu, Chih-ming (Ruth), 1939, 1948-1950; Liu, Fu-lin, 1928; Liu, Shu-fang, 1949; Lo, Hsi-chuang, 1933; Loudenslager, Paul E., 1926-1929; Lu, Ching-shan, 1938, 1954; Ly, Su-hsien, 1933
- Gynecology - Staff - Maxwell, J. Preston, 1914-1932 (Box 64, Folder 453)
- Gynecology - Staff - Maxwell, J. Preston, 1933-1961 (Box 64, Folder 454)
- Gynecology - Staff (Mc-Sz) (Box 65, Folder 455)
  McKelvey, John L., 1934-1941, 1947-1948; Miles, Lee M., 1922-1931, 1962; Moris, Stanley William, 1933; Nielson, Karen M., 1928; Pang, Wen-cheng, 1948; Peng, Chi, 1932; Po, Hing-tsiu, 1948; Pryor, H. B., 1924; Shu, Pei-bwei, 1950; Soong, Hung-chao, 1945-1949; Stevenson, Theodore D., 1936, 1946; Sun, Hui-lun, 1950; Sun, K. C., 1921-1930; Sun, Ming, 1939; Szutu, Liang, 1938-1940
- Gynecology - Staff (Tait - Wang, H. W.) (Box 65, Folder 456)
  Tait, Ruth, 1924; Tang, Ming(g)-yi, 1948-1950; Tang, Yun-the, 1936, 1942, 1945, 1951, 1957, 1971; Teng, Yuet-laan, 1941; Tien, Shueh-ping (Daniel), 1937-1940, 1945-1947; Tong, Helen V., 1933-1934; Toong, Dau-tsu (Theodore), 1941, 1946-1948; Tsang, Yu-teng, 1948; Vincent, Helen, 1921-1923; Wang, Hung-wen, 1938-1948.
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Hung-wen Wang, attached to a letter from Ferguson to Pearce (August 9, 1941), found under the mark-up Gynecology - Staff - Wang.
- Gynecology - Staff (Wang, P. W. - Whitacre) (Box 65, Folder 457)
  Wang, Pei-wo, 1933-1934; Wang, Su-chen, 1924-1926; Wang, Yueh-yun, 1933; Wei, Hsing-chien, 1936; Wei, Shu-chen, 1933-1934; Wen, Chung-li, 1931; Whitacre, Frank E., 1932, 1936-1949, 1953
- Gynecology - Staff (Whitten - Yen) (Box 65, Folder 458)
  Whitten, Edith H., 1924; Wong, Amos, 1924-1934, 194;7 Wong, Wai-tsing, 1933; Woo, Arthur W. T., 1914-1923; Wu, Hieh-chung, 1930; Wu, W. T., 1935; Yang, Pao-hua, 1933-1934; Yang, Ruth P., 1926; Yeh, Hui fang, 1948-1949; Yen, Jen-ying, 1941, 1946-1949
- Gynecology - Staff (Yoh - Yu) (Box 65, Folder 459)
  Yoh, Helen, 1932; Young, Edward S., 1938-1940; Yu, Ai-feng, 1938-1949; Yu, Hsien-ling, 1949-1950
- Hag-Hal (Box 65, Folder 460)
  Hagman, George L., 1946; Hall, Ernest, 1923-1924; Hall, G. Martel, 1944; Hall, Josef W., 1926; Halsey, Marion S., 1921-1928, 1964-1966
- Handbook, 1919-1923, 1935 (Box 65, Folder 461)
  Houghton; McLean; Thompson.
  Items of special note in this folder include maps of Peking.
  See also Box 162, Folder 15
- Handbook, 1935 (Box 66, Folder 462)
  Houghton; McLean;Thompson.
- Harding - Harvard University (Box 66, Folder 463)
  Harding, Warren G., 1923; Harned, Floyd P., 1924-1935, 1946-1948; Harrison, Lucie F., Hospital, 1943; Harvard Medical School of China, 1915, 1926-1927, 1963 (Adams, Charles F.; Barbour; Dashiell; Director; Drew, Edward B.; Moore, Edward C.; Resident Director); Harvard University (Conant, James B., 1933; Cutler, Elliott C., 1932-1933, 1946; Drew, Edward B., 1921; Edsall, David L., 1963; Eliot, Charles W., 1924; Folin, Otto, 1920; Gordon, John E., 1945; Hale, Worth, 1926-1927; Lennox, William G., 1933; Moore, Edward C., 1926, 1931; Putnam, Elizabeth C., 1921; Zinsser, 1926, and see also Zinisser)
  Items of special note in this folder include a photograph of Floyd P. Harned.
- Harvard Yenching Institute - Hayes (Box 66, Folder 464)